Morning.
Miku's back!
Hey.
Hey, how'd it go?
Huh?
It was just a fever. I'm fine.
Not that.
I mean with Asagi-kun.
I bet you couldn't keep
it in your pants.
Tell us everything you can.
Wh-Why would we do anything?!
I had a fever, remember?!
Asagi-kun, Miku's safe.
Asagi-kun?!
He ran off crazy fast.
I never knew Asagi-kun
could run like that.
Right?
I know, right?
How is he so fast?
Well, Miku?
Don't ask me!
Not actually
asleep
Too much attention!
I regret everything.
Do you think those two are going out?
Nah, I doubt that.
They've known each other
since they were kids, though.
Sakura-san's talking to
Asagi-kun all the time, too.
That isn't saying much.
Sakura-san talks to everyone.
Actually, I think Sakura-san's
got a thing for me lately!
I was talking to her about games the other
day, and she burst out laughing.
Sakura-san's so nice. Wow.
Giving you any attention at all...
What's that supposed to mean?!
I mean, Negicchi's decent-looking,
but he's way too much of a loner
to be Sakura-san's boyfriend, no?
Right?
All these popular guys, turning
everything into a pecking order thing...
Nah, there's no way nothing happened.
Like hugging, kissing...
W-We didn't.
Shouldn't you, though?
Someone might take him.
For example, I might.
You gotta open up more.
I've been trying not to think about him.
Everyone talking about Yukiya
is reminding me.
I can't!
I need more Yukiya!
I Want to End This Love Game
Weird...
Episode 12
My Childhood Friend Is Girly
We've always had some space
between us in class,
but now these moments
feel really lonely.
I can't wait to be next to him.
What would he say if I said we
should hang out again after school?
Would it seem too desperate
if I kept going?
I want to glom onto Yukiya!
So I thought I might make him some cake
or something to thank him for visiting.
Cake?!
That's pretty western.
Western?
You sound like Yukiya when
he sees the popular kids.
Japanese snacks are nice.
Family runs a Japanese snack shop
They're hand-sized because
they're each made carefully by hand.
The gentle, relaxing sweetness
spreads through your mouth.
They're the very embodiment
of love, don't you think?
Are you serious?
High school girls making
Japanese snacks as a gift?
Actually, I used to make ohagi
with my grandma every year.
It was fun rolling them up and
wrapping them and stuff together.
Right?
And can you do that with western snacks?
Knead,
knead
Yeah, yeah!
I like that!
Also...
Wakana always steals one
whenever I buy mochi ice cream.
My dream is to eat two someday.
Nacchan, do you know how
to make daifuku mochi?
Of course! I'm a big girl!
Mochi Flour
Ta-da!
What's all this?
Stuff for making Japanese snacks.
I wanted to thank you for
taking care of me the other day.
Mochi tastes better fresh, you know?
So I figured maybe
I'd make it at your place.
You don't need to thank me.
I guess I'll have it if you
insist on making me some.
Is she telling me to
make some with her?
Heh heh
Look, ice cream!
We're making red bean paste
and ice cream together!
This is gonna be fun.
Look at her, blabbing away so happily.
So, this is the recipe video
Nacchan recommended.
Mochi Flour
Hey.
Yo, Miku.
I told you to pause there for a second.
Why're you so spaced out?
That startled me.
There are pink ones
and light green ones.
Pretty.
Tiny
Yours looks shiratama-sized.
Wha? Yours is just too huge.
How are you going to eat that?
It's not that bad.
Here.
I-It's too huge!
Even with my mouth,
it'll take three bites!
Yeah?
I guess it's a bit big.
Wait, I can't.
I've touched his hand and gotten
close to him and stuff before.
There really is something wrong with me.
S-Stay calm. Stay calm.
Yukiya, Yukiya.
Does this make you think of anything?
Huh?
Hold on...
Cherry blossom color
and green onion color!
It's like we're clinging to each other.
Isn't that titillating?
Did you put them together on purpose?
Isn't that titillating?!
Doubling down, huh?
So the pink one is you, then.
I wonder how this Miku tastes.
What's wrong?
Is it like I just ate you?
Does that turn you on?
Man, that's good.
Of course it is!
I'm going to go wash my hands!
I can almost feel Miku's
warmth on it still.
Miku's lips were about as soft.
Was Yukiya always like this?
His voice, his hands, his figure...
Everything makes my heart race.
Maybe I'm so in love with Yukiya
that my senses are glitching out.
Nom, nom, nom, nom...
Nom
Miku
Miku...
Nom
Ew!
Flinch
I'm home.
What?! How?!
I was just eating the mochi!
That's the creepiest
possible way to eat it!
Those two are flirting again.
I'm going to get heartburn again.
I should have salted kombu
for my afternoon snack.
I Want to End This Love Game
Lewd!
S-Senpai, keep your voice down!
B-But...
How could the Pokitto game
end up developing into that?!
Tell me more.
What more am I supposed to say?
How many times did you do it?
I don't remember.
You did so much
that you don't even remember?!
That's too obscene!
Tell me in detail how you did it.
I-I think, in the beginning,
we were both really cautious.
Kinda like that.
Yukiya's hand slowly
came toward my shoulder,
and then he held me firmer, and...
C-Can I stop?!
I'm a girl!
N-No! You're the only one
I can ask, Sakura-san!
And then?
How did you feel doing it?
Sports Festival
I thought it might be a bit risky.
Risky?
I was paralyzed from my head to my toes.
My mind went blank.
And...
I could feel myself going stupid.
Wait, wait.
And that turned into a lewd,
masochistic situation, correct?
I-It did not!
You're a girl, after all.
I am a girl.
I'm worried that Yukiya
might regret kissing me.
Why?
I mean, he might think I'm manipulative.
I used a kiss to take advantage
of his male urges.
I'm horrible.
I let my need for approval
take over. So nasty.
I'm such a trash girl.
I want to become a girl
he can be glad he kissed.
That was my conclusion.
A bunch of stuff happened,
but it brought us closer together.
I decided I want to become even cuter.
So let me know if you wanna talk again.
Sakura-san is amazing.
She just kissed the man she loves,
and instead of getting carried away,
she's thinking about
other people's needs.
I put a lot on her plate,
but she did what she could
to help me even though I'm older.
And...
I want to become a girl
he can be glad he kissed.
Can I ever become one?
Miku. Lots to do, huh?
Thanks for helping out.
Hey, no problem.
I brought snacks.
For you, too, President.
Thanks.
I'm the Pokitto granny monster!
You're the what?
Gimme.
Kazane!
Why didn't you tell me
you still had more to do?
I was about to go home.
But you're busy with work and stuff.
You shouldn't overwork.
"Overwork."
I've got stamina. Don't worry.
You're always keeping an eye
on the student council
so we aren't overburdened.
Just be sure it doesn't all
end up on your shoulders.
Kakeru.
Want one?
A few minutes later
I said it! I said it! I said it!
Grandma...
Grandma's calling me again.
Sakura-san?!
Sakura-san!
Grandma...
Once again, Sakura Miku's life
flashed before her eyes.
She recovered in the
nurse's office
Café
Oh yeah, Yukiya, what are you
competing in on sports day?
I haven't decided yet.
Akane and I were thinking we
should make cheerleading merch.
Wanna help?
Why would I say yes?
I don't know how to interact
with them. Too much work.
Are you sure?
I was going to make one
specially for you.
Yukiya
Yukiya! Yukiya!
Heart skip a beat?
Are you crazy?
Think about how everyone
else is going to react.
Who cares?
I care!
They're taking forever!
They're obviously in
love with each other.
Why are they taking so long?
They should just confess
and get it over with.
Though...
The fact they can't is what
makes them who they are.
I say we watch them struggle
and figure it out for themselves.
It's their youth to experience.
You're so old, preaching
about youth like that.
But you're right, I think.
But they're so slow!
Supomon is the best!
Kids' Supomon
Sparrows, and Yukiya's flyaways
from this morning
I love Miku.
Things would be so much easier
if I could just tell her that.
Miku's irreplaceable to me.
Which is why, even if I let
her cuteness overwhelm me,
even if I admit defeat in the Love Game,
even if we start dating...
Even if things work out now,
it might fall apart because
she's too good for me.
At this sports day
and during the summer...
I'll become such an attractive guy
that you'll be devastated.
1 new message
Just now
I have to talk to you after school.
Wait for me in class.
By yourself.
Just now
45 sheets
Origami
I'm making flowers for Grandma!
45 sheets
Origami
Today
I have to talk to you after school.
Wait for me in class.
Just now
Read
Got it!
By yourself.
You're helping me!
Okay, sure, but...
Grandma will be so happy!
Oh yeah, you used to
make origami at my place.
1,000 sheets
45 sheets
Origami
Yup. And we're doing
hydrangeas this month.
She already started
Fold, fold
Fold,
fold
Don't you think hydrangeas
and snails look cute together?
I heard there aren't too many snails
on hydrangeas because they're poisonous.
Although, it's not supposed to be too bad
as long as they don't eat the leaves.
Some people say they'll flee
if you put the leaves next to them.
They just happen to be there
because it's the summer rainy season.
Here you go again, being annoying.
Who cares? It's cute.
See?
Poor thing, getting poisoned
because of our human egos...
These ones aren't poisonous, okay?
School is now closing.
Any students in the building,
please finish your activities
and prepare to make your way home.
Look at the time.
That was fast.
Wanna go?
I love hydrangeas.
You do? Why?
They're so aesthetic.
So puffy and pretty.
Depending on the type,
the flower language is nice, too.
"Together with family."
Perfect for Grandma, right?
Ah, yes, yes, I get it.
In other words,
you were trying to tell me
you want me to be part of your family.
Wha?!
Get over yourself, idiot!
Though...
I wouldn't mind if you
and I started a family.
Well? Breathless now?
You know...
There's something you need to say
before we start a family.
You know that, right?
I love you! Marry me!
You need to ask my dad for my hand.
Look at him, taking it seriously!
You definitely have
feelings for me, don't you?
That's not it!
Ugh...
That'll have to come after
I win the game, I guess.
Sure.
Miku...
I love you.
Me, too.
I love you, Yukiya.